(Penny(on phone):)No, I did not see it coming.
(Penny(on phone):)No, we did not set a date.
No, I'm not pregnant.
(Penny(on phone):)Yeah, this is a first for our family.
(Penny(on phone):)All right, tell Dad I love him.
I gotta go. All right, bye.
(Amy:)-Atomic magnets?
-Shut up.
Sony I'm late.
The leaf blower broke,
(Bernadette:)so I had to hand-dry
my mother-in-law.
(Penny:)-You want some wine?
-Thanks.
(Bernadette:)Little warning before you jump
(Bernadette:)you're not just marrying him,
you're marrying his family.
(Penny:)I think Leonard's mom's okay with me.
(Bernadette:)It doesn't matter if she's okay
(Bernadette:)can she go
to the bathroom by herself?
(Bernadette:)Hit me again.
(Amy:)So, what are the living
arrangements gonna be?
(Penny:)Well, haven't really talked
about it yet, but I figure,
(Penny:)at some point, I'll move in
with him, or he'll move in with me.
(Amy:)Well, with you not working,
that makes financial sense.